I'll be happy if I keep a promise
Of course, you're always the same
It's okay, it's okay
If you don't want to say it, I'll be the same
So happy, I'll be the same
If you're crying, I'll be laughing
The time when the light shines
There will be a smile on your lips
With you, with you, with you
If you love me,
I'll be able to be with you for a long time
I can't believe how I feel
I'm in trouble
If I take a serious test,
I'll become a big fan of you
I'm a big fan of you
I was able to meet you
I don't know where you are
I don't know how you're going to be back
I don't have any troubles
I don't know how you'll be
I don't know how you will react
I was looking forward to seeing you again!
The other two?
Everyone, you have to hurry!
I'm sorry!
I didn't do anything wrong!
Don't think about it!
Why did you do that?
I did it like this!
It's hard for you to become a teacher!
I was worried because I was scared.
It's time for me to start.
Come on!
I'll teach you a pen pencil!
I'm scared!
I was scared.
I was scary because I wasn't able to make a video for you!
It's dangerous to see me.
What is it?
I was not saying that.
I felt more crying.
I'm not crying anymore.
I thought I could play with you before you became Aura.
I'm flattered.
Oh, no!
Ah, it's a cat.
What are you doing, Kamukan?
Oh, no.
You don't have to be scared.
Who are you? Are you going to live here?
Huh?
What's that?
I didn't see that.
It's not a cat, it's a cat, it's a cat.
I'm scared.
I'm scared?
You're going to live with me?
I'm going to live with you.
Really?
Yes.
That's right.
It's a little bit of a little bit of a baby.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's right.
I'm going to live.
Okay, I'm coming.
Bye.
I'm coming.
You're so good.
I'm doing well.
Ranu, you want to live?
Unfortunately, I am allowed to live.
I can't do that either.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Hang on.
The editor...
Huh...
Hey, the weather's so nice, this is like the sea.
But...
Ah...
I don't want to go anymore.
I mean, theirie leader is on the ship.
I must leave.
No.
I'm not leaving.
We're just a couple of minutes away from here.
That's not a big deal.
Hey, let's try a little bit.
Just a little bit.
Is that okay?
It's done!
Ready...
Let's go!
Are you alright?
It's done!
Is this how it looks like?
It's a little dangerous.
What is it now?
It's a little dangerous, Ranga-san.
That's it!
That's the part!
It's a little dangerous, Ranga-san.
It's dangerous, Ranga-san.
Are you okay, Ranga-san?
I can't forgive you for that.
Ita-zura-ni-shite wa, a little too much rock.
The first day of the day.
What are you going to do today?
What should we do today?
I can't see you well.
I was going to play with you in the morning.
I was going to play with you in the bathroom.
Are you going to play with me?
No, I'm sorry that I was late.
What?
Are you okay now?
I'm okay.
Are you okay?
I see. That's good.
Well, be safe at that time.
Okay.
That's a lot of fun!
What are you doing here?
You can't go anywhere!
Hurry up and get out of here!
Yeah, that's right.
Everyone, make your own food.
Who's the longest to eat?
Oh, it's cold.
It's cold.
What are you doing here?
Everyone, make your own food!
It's cold!
I'm so sleepy.
I'm always sleepy, right?
Oh, you're so nice.
Really?
But, there's only one condition for this shape.
For example,
the shape and the balance are the same.
It's lighter than anything else.
That's right!
I'm so sleepy.
What are you doing here?
Oh!
I'll put it in here!
I'm sleepy.
Why are you sleepy?
I'm not sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
What?
What's wrong?
I'm sleepy.
Did you say you're sleepy?
What's wrong?
I'm sleepy.
Then, who said you're sleepy?
What?
I'm sleepy.
Are you sleepy?
I can't believe it.
I'm sleepy.
Damn it.
I'm sleepy too.
What?
What's wrong?
Let's go home.
Hey, Hazuki!
You're late.
What?
Yes.
It's delicious.
Hazuki!
Hazuki, what are you doing?
What's wrong, Dad?
Dad?
What's wrong with you?
No.
You can't eat the food you've eaten, Dad.
You can't eat it?
It's just before.
Dad, what do you think of Hazuki?
It's good.
What's wrong?
Is it a fish?
It's a fish.
It's delicious.
Hey!
I can't eat anything.
It's delicious.
Hazuki.
Wait!
I'll eat it later.
Is it a fish?
I like it.
It's a fish.
I can't eat anything.
I may die, but I'll do my best.
It's okay if it's only a smoke.
I can't eat anything.
I'm glad you're here.
Why is it so cute?
Is it a fish?
I can't eat anything.
It's a fish.
What is it?
You can eat anything.
I can't eat anything.
Oh, it's a fish.
Aren't you going to eat something at home?
Oh, no.
I have a Sunday.
But it's pretty good.
It smells better if I then thought.
Not bad at all!
Today's the day I get sick.
It's so famous food on listeners' tables.
He has no friends anymore!
He likes it so much like he's going to win.
He's supporting us and enjoying it.
Look out!
Let's go!
Huh?
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!!
What's going on?
Isn't this the face we ate?
No, it's not that cool from before!
You're really an idiot, aren't you?
Is that cute girl again?
She's not like that, right, idiot?
Hey!
Come on!
No, Uiba!
I'm sorry for being late.
I thought I'd be late, but...
What?
Idiot!
You were worried about me, weren't you?
Idiot?
That's right!
You've always been here since you were a kid.
You're so kind to me.
You're cute, aren't you?
Hey!
If you're happy, you can stop me tonight.
I like you.
If you're on the other side, you're on the other side.
Huh?
That's...
You're so cute!
That's right.
You're probably so cute.
Why?
You're here with me right now!
No!
You're so cute!
Hey!
What's the matter, Yusu?
What's going on?
You're so kind to me.
I'm going to put you on the floor and eat you up.
Idiot!
I know.
I thought you were different from usual.
I'm not sure if you're not going to laugh at me right now.
I see.
Huh?
I'm sure you're really going to laugh.
I see.
I think you're going to laugh.
I don't want you to laugh anymore.
Don't laugh.
I...
I'll show you now!
I'll show you today!
Why?
You're going to teach me what when I see!
Right!
I don't teach you.
I want to try to see someone as a teacher.
I wonder if I can put it in my friend's hand.
Eh?
It's not a joke, it's a story.
That's right. I didn't do anything wrong.
But I think I can do it.
Karousuke, I want to study together with you.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you angry with everyone?
Karousuke, what's wrong with you?
I don't want to do it.
That's right, I don't want to do it.
I'm not going to go to the bathroom.
What?
I'm really sorry.
I don't want to go to the bathroom with everyone.
I'll listen to you when you're in the bathroom.
What are you doing?
Hey, Karousuke!
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Karousuke, where are you?
What's wrong with you?
Karousuke, if you're happy, let's play together.
Hey, you guys.
It's not a joke.
I don't want to do it.
That's what I thought.
What's wrong with you?
Hey!
Stop it!
Karousuke!
Let's go.
What's wrong with you?
I'm not letting you go.
I don't want to be with you.
I'm some crap, you know.
Hey!
I want to ask you something.
Are you ignoring me?
I'm sorry.
Is that a misunderstanding?
It's all my fault.
Well done, everyone.
That's right!
It doesn't seem like it's going to break up!
Alright! Let's try it once more!
Yay!
What's going on?
I can't believe it!
I can't believe it's going to break up!
Ah...
I'm glad I was able to get along with Kawasaki.
You're right. I'm not scared of the water.
That's right. I'm glad you're here.
It's been a long time since I last saw you.
Oh, you're getting stronger.
Oh, no! Rock!
I told you to step on that stone!
Okay, baby!
I'll kill you!
It's a lot of fun.
We got the fire!
A-A-A-A!
It's a natural fire!
I got you!
I didn't expect this to happen.
I see.
So that's...
It's a river.
It's okay!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'm fine.
Hey!
If you go to Tokyo,
we'll go to the river next time.
I came to the river.
We'll be together to the river.
Huh?
That guy?
No, no, no!
Hey, Doc!
We know each other very well.
That's right.
We can go to the river.
So we can go.
I don't know.
I was just kidding.
Then that's...
If I were you...
That guy is really lonely.
I want to go to the river next time.
I see.
Where is that guy?
The river...
It's not a big deal.
That guy...
It's true.
He's the only one in the river.
Maybe he's the only one there.
The river...
He's the only one there.
He's waiting for us.
It's true that I came out from the river.
Is it true that there's treasure in the river?
Yeah!
It's a game center in Sakasa's room.
I see.
Yeah!
There's a lot of monsters!
I'm here!
Next time on Mokomukapara Dice,
Mokomukapara Dice,
I'll be back with another fun!